<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>structural inequalities | Jiyoun Suk</title>
    <link>/tag/structural-inequalities/</link>
      <atom:link href="/tag/structural-inequalities/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>structural inequalities</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© Jiyoun Suk 2020</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/images/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>structural inequalities</title>
      <link>/tag/structural-inequalities/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community, context, and communication</title>
      <link>/project/community-context-communication/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/project/community-context-communication/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I examine how the cultural, political, and social contexts surrounding individuals would interplay with networked communication flows to shape political judgments. I emphasize the importance of understanding communication patterns and public opinion formation across differing levels of social, cultural, and political structures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Selected publications and manuscripts in progress:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Suk, J.&lt;/strong&gt;, Shah, D., Wells, C, Wagner, M., Friedland, L., Cramer, K., Hughes, C., &amp;amp; Franklin, C. (2020). Do Improving Conditions Harden Partisan Preferences? Communication, Context, and Political Evaluations During Periods of Contention. &lt;em&gt;International Journal of Public Opinion Research&lt;/em&gt;. doi: 10.1093/ijpor/edz051&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Suk, J.&lt;/strong&gt;, McLeod, D., &amp;amp; Shah, D. Am I with Her or with&amp;hellip;Him?: How Political Contextual Factors Drove Public and Online Participation in the 2016 US Presidential Election.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Li, J., &lt;strong&gt;Suk, J.&lt;/strong&gt;, Lukito, J., Hughes, C., Foley, J., Friedland, L., Wells, C., Shah, D., &amp;amp; Wagner, M. When the Desert Matters: Contextual Differences in Local News Environment and Polarized Perceptions of Local Economy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Su, M., &lt;strong&gt;Suk, J.&lt;/strong&gt;, &amp;amp; Rojas, H. Online news sharing, political extremity and reduced network interaction in China, Japan, South Korea, and the US: An imagined audience approach.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Suk, J&lt;/strong&gt;, Coppini, D., Muiz, C., &amp;amp; Rojas, H. &amp;ldquo;The More You Know, the Less You Like&amp;rdquo;: How News and Political Talk Shape Political Knowledge and Affective Polarization in Colombia, Mexico and the United States.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
