<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>network analysis | Jiyoun Suk</title>
    <link>https://jiyounsuk.github.io/tag/network-analysis/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://jiyounsuk.github.io/tag/network-analysis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>network analysis</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© Jiyoun Suk 2020</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://jiyounsuk.github.io/images/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>network analysis</title>
      <link>https://jiyounsuk.github.io/tag/network-analysis/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Politics and Activism</title>
      <link>https://jiyounsuk.github.io/project/digital-politics-and-activism/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jiyounsuk.github.io/project/digital-politics-and-activism/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Focusing on the shifting communication ecologies and changing media environment, this line of research investigates the dynamics of (dis/mis)information flows, their relationships with external events and news media coverage, and democratic consequences such as political actions and social trust. Some of my research further look at dissemination of Russian disinformation messages in online sphere and their infiltration into the US media system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Selected publications and manuscripts in progress:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Suk, J.&lt;/strong&gt;, Abhishek, A., Zhang, Y., Ahn, S. Y., Correa, T., Garlough, C., &amp;amp; Shah, D. V. (2019).#MeToo, Networked Acknowledgment, and Connective Action: How &amp;ldquo;Empowerment Through Empathy&amp;rdquo; Launched a Social Movement. &lt;em&gt;Social Science Computer Review&lt;/em&gt;. doi: 10.1177/0894439319864882&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lukito, J., &lt;strong&gt;Suk, J.&lt;/strong&gt;, Zhang, Y., Doroshenko, L., Su, M., Kim, S. J., Xia, Y., Freelon, D., &amp;amp; Wells, C. (2019) The Wolves in Sheep&amp;rsquo;s Clothing: How Russia&amp;rsquo;s Internet Research Agency Tweets Appeared in U.S. News as Vox Populi. &lt;em&gt;International Journal of Press/Politics&lt;/em&gt;. doi: 10.1177/1940161219895215&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zhang, Y., Shah, D., Foley, J., Abhishek, A., Lukito, J., &lt;strong&gt;Suk, J.&lt;/strong&gt;, Kim, S., Sun, Z., Pevehouse, J. &amp;amp; Garlough, C. (2019). Whose Lives Matter? Mass Shootings and Social Media Discourses of Sympathy and Policy, 2012-2014. &lt;em&gt;Journal of Computer-Mediated Communication&lt;/em&gt;, 24(4), 182-202. doi: 10.1093/jcmc/zmz009&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ghosh, S., Su, M., Aman, A., &lt;strong&gt;Suk, J.&lt;/strong&gt;, Tong, C., Hills, O., Correa, T., Garlough, C., Borah, P., &amp;amp; Shah, D. (2020). Covering #MeToo Across the News Spectrum: Political Accusation and
Public Events as Drivers of Press Attention. &lt;em&gt;International Journal of Press/Politics&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zhang, Y., Wang, Y., Foley, J., &lt;strong&gt;Suk, J.&lt;/strong&gt;, &amp;amp; Conathan, D. (2017, July). Tweeting mass shootings: the dynamics of issue attention on social media. In &lt;em&gt;Proceedings of the 8th International Conference on Social Media &amp;amp; Society&lt;/em&gt; (pp. 1-5).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Suk, J.&lt;/strong&gt;, Lukito, J., Su, M., Kim, S. J., Tong, C., Sun, Z., &amp;amp; Sarma, P. Do I sound American? Predicting Disinformation Sharing of Russian IRA tweets from a Linguistic Perspective.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Suk, J.&lt;/strong&gt;, Zhang, Y., Lukito, J., Su, M., &amp;amp; Foley, J. Tracing Twitter Buzz: Clustering Hashtags and Handles About Mass Shootings and Gun Control.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shah, D., &lt;strong&gt;Suk, J.&lt;/strong&gt;, &amp;amp; McLeod, D. Breaking the “Virtuous Circle”: How Partisan Communication Flows Can Erode Social Trust but Drive Participation.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
